Using the given class of a heap with the minimal element in the root (min heap) which is using static memory representation of a tree, implement a method which adds a given positive value to the given element value (mind method efficiency, do not delete and insert new elements into the heap ). If the element does not exist, do not change the heap. Check the method for different use cases calling from the main method.
